nplusonemag.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy | n+1

## 1\. Overview

We at n+1 Foundation (the “Foundation,” “we,” “our,” or “us”) are committed to protecting the privacy and security of visitors to our website and those who purchase products from our Website (as defined in the [Terms and Conditions](http://nplusonemag.com/about/terms/)). This Privacy Policy is part of the Terms and Conditions of the Website and describes what information we gather on the Website and how it is used.

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. By using our Website, or any of the products or resources that we provide on our Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you should not use our Website, and your continued use of our Website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean that you accept those changes.

## 2\. Collection and Use of Information

### What Information About You is Collected on Our Website?

We collect information that identifies you or can be used to identify or contact you (“Personally Identifiable Information”), which may include your name, address, email address, telephone number, and billing and credit card information. We also collect your login time and date, your IP address, the pages you viewed (as well as the time and date viewed), and your order history.

You do not have to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information to visit our Website. However, if you choose to withhold requested information, you may not be able to purchase our products online, such as a subscription to n+1 or a book or other merchandise available in our [online store](http://shop.nplusonemag.com/) (the “Store”).

### Where and When Information is Collected on Our Website

We may collect Personally Identifiable Information from you in different manners and at different places on our Website, such as when you subscribe to the print or online editions of the magazine or purchase books or other products or when you sign up to receive our newsletter. In addition, when you purchase a subscription to n+1, purchase any product from the Store, or make a donation on the Website, Personally Identifiable Information is collected by us and by one or more of our third party e-commerce partners: Shopify, Stripe, MemberMouse, Braintree, Mailchimp, and/or PayPal, as well as other e-commerce partners we may utilize from time to time. We will collect Personally Identifiable Information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us or as otherwise indicated in this Privacy Policy.

The website is not intended for users under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from users under the age of 13. Such users are expressly prohibited from submitting their Personally Identifiable Information to us.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. The Foundation uses cookies to identify and track visitors, track usage of the Website and access preferences. Website visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Website, with the drawback that certain features of the Website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Use of Information that We Collect

In general, we use the information collected on our Website to help us understand who uses our Website, to improve our Website. We also use it to collect payments you made in our [Store](http://shop.nplusonemag.com/), when you [Subscribe](http://nplusonemag.com/subscribe/), and when you [Donate](http://nplusonemag.com/donate/), as well as to fulfill your orders. We also use it to solicit subscription renewals, new subscriptions, orders for merchandise, and contributions to the Foundation. In addition, we may send you information on new products or upcoming events. However, if you do not wish to receive emailed marketing messages from us, please let us know by sending an email to webmaster@nplusonemag.com.

### When We Disclose Information to Third Parties

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose any information we gather from you on our Website.

We may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information if we believe in good faith that we are required by law to do so. We may also disclose your Personally Identifiable Information in order for us to cooperate with official investigations or legal proceedings. We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information in special circumstances when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to protect the safety and/or security of our users, our Website, or the general public.

We may employ independent contractors, vendors, or suppliers (collectively, “Outside Contractors”) to provide specific services and products related to our Website or products, such as providing credit card processing and fraud screening and fulfilling purchase orders. Access to your Personally Identifiable Information by these Outside Contractors is limited to the information we believe is reasonably necessary in order for the Outside Contractors to perform their limited functions for us. We also require that these contractors (i) protect the privacy of your Personally Identifiable Information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy, and (ii) not use or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information for any purpose other than providing us with products or services for which we contracted. You should also refer to the websites of our e-commerce partners referred to above for their privacy policies.

We may also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance and market research, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services.

In addition, through our Website, you may be given the opportunity to purchase (or obtain more information regarding) certain content, products, or services which are sold through a person or company other than us (collectively, “Third Party Sellers”). Third Party Sellers may request that you submit certain information to them in order to purchase their products or services or to obtain additional information from them. By submitting the requested information, you affirmatively consent to have that information shared with the Third Party Seller. This information is used by the Third Party Seller and may be subject to a different Privacy Policy. We do not otherwise share or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to Third-Party Sellers except as set forth in this policy.

We may from time to time sell, lease, rent, or exchange our subscriber lists, customer lists, and contact lists (which will not include credit card information, but may include other Personally Identifiable Information). Right now we don’t do too much of this. And we don’t let just anyone use our lists.

We reserve the right to transfer information to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, or other transfer of all or a significant portion of the assets of the Foundation provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the terms of this or its own Privacy Policy. We will notify users of any such transfer through notice on our Website and, to the extent possible, through email.

### Does this Privacy Policy Apply When We Link to Other Websites?

Our Website contains links to other websites not owned or operated by the Foundation. We are not responsible for the content, accuracy, privacy practices, and performance of those websites or for any cookies they may place on your computer. We encourage you to be aware when our Website links to other websites and read the privacy policies or statements of each and every website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected by our Website.

### Is the Information We Collect Secure?

We strive to secure transmission of your Personally Identifiable Information from your computer to our servers through industry-standard techniques. To help ensure the integrity and privacy of the Personally Identifiable Information you provide via the internet at the time you purchase any product or donate online, the above mentioned third party e-commerce partners Shopify, Stripe, MemberMouse, Braintree, Mailchimp, and/or PayPal, as well as other e-commerce partners we may utilize from time to time, provide Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) digital security. Only employees, contractors, and volunteers of the Foundation who need access to your Personally Identifiable Information to perform a specific task or function are granted access to such Personally Identifiable Information. Notwithstanding the foregoing, no employee, contractor, or volunteer of the Foundation will have access to your credit card information provided through this Website.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the internet. There is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart our security systems. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

### Choices that You Have Regarding the Collection, Disclosure, and Distribution of Personally Identifiable Information

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will only use Personally Identifiable Information for the purposes described above or as otherwise disclosed at the time we request such information from you. You may “opt-out” of receiving other communications by contacting our Webmaster at the address set out below.

## 3\. General Information

### Updating and Correcting Your Personally Identifiable Information

You can always contact us in order to (1) update or correct your Personally Identifiable Information, (2) change your preferences with respect to communications and other information you may receive from us, or (3) delete the Personally Identifiable Information maintained about you on our systems, by contacting our Webmaster at the address set out below. Such updates, corrections, changes, and deletions will not have an effect on other information that we maintain, or information that we have provided to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy prior to such update, correction, change, or deletion.

You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us on our systems. The need to back up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your Personally Identifiable Information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate. After receiving your request, all Personally Identifiable Information stored in databases we actively use and other readily searchable media will be promptly updated, corrected, changed, or deleted as appropriate.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

If at any point we decide to use Personally Identifiable Information in a manner we deem significantly different from that stated in this Privacy Policy, or otherwise disclosed to you, at the time it was collected, we will notify you by posting changes on our Website in this Privacy Policy, or by email or otherwise, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your Personally Identifiable Information in the new manner. We may also make non-significant changes to our Privacy Policy that generally will not affect our use of your Personally Identifiable Information.

### Contact Regarding Privacy Questions

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or feel that we are not abiding by the terms of our posted Privacy Policy, please contact us:

Webmaster  
n+1 Foundation  
68 Jay Street #405  
New York, NY 10012  
webmaster@nplusonemag.com

_Last updated: June 19, 2014_
